I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Oh well...
Stop...
Stop!
Koyuki is the best!
Have you lost your mind?
What the hell are you saying
all of a sudden?
I said Koyuki is the best.
The vocalist for your band's
gotta be Koyuki.
He's a genius. He's gonna
be a fucking great vocalist.
Hey, we're not talking about
making the choir here, understand?
Now really, you don't understand!
What are they fighting about?
I can't understand them at all.
I think Koyuki will be great too!
Huh?!
The vocalist for the band.
I think Koyuki will be good!
Vocalist?
Koyuki and Chiba, huh?
W-what? What're you looking at?!
Yukio! You have a letter from Hiro-kun!
"How are you, Yukio-kun?
I'm doing very well right now."
"I won the Kyushu
Piano Contest the other day!"
"Do you know how big that is?
I might even go to Vienna!"
"P.S. I bought the latest Sangokushi."
Let's see...
"Dear Hiro-kun,"
"Thank you for your letter.
I've started playing the guitar."
"It's surprisingly easy to play."
"I've mastered music played
by Van Halen, Steve Vai,
Paul Gilbert, Nuno, Zakk Wylde,
and even Yot-chan..."
"I'm practicing
'The Song of the Seasons' right now."
"Wouldn't it be great if we
could play together in Vienna?"
"The photo I've enclosed was taken
at the East Japan Guitar Awards
held at the municipal gymnasium."
"It's from when I won in
the middle school division."
"Yours truly..."
Mom, I'm going to the gymnasium!
What am I doing anyway?
It's almost summer vacation...
All right! First, I'm gonna
find me a giant beetle!
Today's cloudy skies
will clear up with time
Go for it, don't be tied down,
set yourself free
Feel free, yes,
the new tomorrow is wow wow
So cheer up,
because I want to see your smile
H-hello...
I-I'm sorry!
Who was that kid?
Koyuki.
-About time you leave.
-Huh? Forget that kid.
Go home!
He's more important than me?
Yeah.
You felt differently yesterday!
You were so nice yesterday...
You're the pits!
-Yo!
-I-I'm sorry!
Granny's not here now.
Let's practice a song.
Ryusuke-kun...I...
I have to talk to you.
What is it?
Get the fuck outta here!
Never come around again.
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry...I'm sorry...
I'm sorry...I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
All right!
First, get the lane markers
and we'll go 200 meters four times!
-Are you serious?!
-We'll die!
I won't allow any slacking!
This summer, we're gonna get
way better than the rival schools!
Umm...What about my plans
as team advisor?
Boy, that interim coach is tough.
It's only been two weeks,
but he's way more than interim!
If this keeps up, everyone will
quit the team! But he sure is tough!
Saito-san is a fanatic who swims
over 30,000 meters every week!
It's like, is he really 44?!
By the way, isn't Koyuki-kun
joining the team?
He's in a bit of a bind right now.
-Bind?
-Yeah.
I wonder if he's okay.
Hey, you two girls! No slacking!
-Sorry!
Yukio, you have a letter from Hiro-kun!
"I'm shocked you started
playing the guitar."
"But I bet you're still
no match for my piano skills."
"I wanna hear how good you are.
Play for me whenever I visit next."
"P.S. I didn't get to go to Vienna,
but I did visit Holland Town."
Huh? Koyuki-kun, right?
Yes.
Did something happen? I haven't
seen you at the pool since then.
No.
You play the guitar?
Err...no...
-This is...
-Oh boy, that's bad!
Yes...
Once it's broken...
Broken things can't be fixed.
-I wonder about that.
-Huh?
This guitar can probably be fixed.
My friend will do it for cheap.
Give it a month and it'll be fixed.
It can be fixed?
Saito-san...
I may not look like it,
but British rock changed my life.
Saito-san...
Poor guitar, if you throw it away.
Come on over anytime,
and bring that guitar.
If you'd like, I'd be happy to teach you.
See you!
All right.
This is pitiful...
About Koyuki...
That guitar was given to me by Eddie.
No one would give me the time of day...
And it was Eddie who took the time
to talk to this Japanese kid.
But even Koyuki...
Ryusuke-kun...
Hey! Look, look!
Look what I got!
-Hey, Ryusuke! Help me!
-Huh?
Here you are, Izumi-chan!
Oh, thanks...
-Don't mention it!
-Huh? What about for me?
-It was hilarious the other day...
-Huh?
Ryusuke's never eaten natto in his life.
-Huh?! You serious?!
-So
Hey. It's almost time.
-Right.
Man, who cares about the concert?
-Don't you want to make
summer memories with me?
-Let's go!
Hey! I'm coming, too! C'mon!
It'd be the perfect double date!
Can't think of a band without him.
Yeah, definitely funky.
Man, the vocals were terrible!
What the hell-?!
With vocals like that,
I feel sorry for Taira.
Why you-!
Good evening, everyone!
I'm Manabu and I used to
do vocals with The Crowd!
-Manabu!
-Sing for us!
You're so cool!
Switch with me, you're terrible.
Why you-!
Sing, Manabu!
Ryusuke-kun...
I know. This was Eiji's idea.
Well, since I'm on stage,
maybe I'll sing.
The Music Men are here,
so maybe I'll sing "Journey"
by the Heartbreakers!
What'll we do?
Hurry and sing!
Who's calling my name?
I hear the voice of legends
What do I want?
Static emotion comes down
Did I have the dream?
Am I misunderstood?
What do I want?
Static emotion comes down
-I'm going home.
-What?
I don't know what's good about him at all.
"Saito Paper Company"
That's it! F is played by
pressing down with your index finger.
Hmm...pretty good.
Really?
You're progressing nicely.
You can make sounds now.
Yeah.
Now that you've gotten
the hang of common chords,
let's try to play continuously.
Uhh...My fingers...
Hurt, don't they?
But if you give up now,
you won't make it with girls.
No, that's not what I-
Koyuki-kun. Observe.
T-that's amazing!
Koyuki-kun, come with me.
Okay.
When I got injured and had
my Olympic dreams shattered,
I felt so sorry for myself,
and my only consolation...
...was guitars!
Which one do you like, Koyuki-kun?
The guitar on the left is
the same shape as Ryusuke-kun's!
Oh...I'll bet that one
is a Gibson Les Paul.
But mine is a fake
called the Tibson Les Paul.
When it was 360 yen to the dollar,
I couldn't afford the real McCoy.
Tibson?
Now then...I'll let you
borrow this Les Paul.
Huh?! Are you sure?!
You'll also need a tuning machine,
and...an amp.
Fool! Fool! Fool! Fool! Fool!
"My name is Page."
-Fool! Fool! Fool! Fool! Fool!
-Page?
Ever heard of a band
called the Rocket Boys?
Fool!
They're a mystery British group,
overshadowed by the Beatles,
who recorded one album
and then broke up.
They're the teachers of my soul.
Follow me
Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
-And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
-A-amazing!
-And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
-I've never seen a bird like that,
even on TV.
That's Page.
The one and only friend of Kenichi Saito,
age 44 and unmarried.
Fool!
Making him sing is my goal.
Dammit!
He'll only respond to great music!
Koyuki-kun! Let's do our best
to make Page sing!
All right! If I'm going to try,
I may as well give it my best!
That's the spirit, Koyuki-kun!
Just wait! We'll make him sing for us!
Yes! Atta boy, Koyuki-kun!
Of the three feudal generals,
I like Nobunaga the best.
Fool!
Okay then, let's start today's practice!
All right! Please teach me!
A!
D!
G!
F!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
The road comes to a fork.
"Next Episode"
Isn't love so painful?